<archimate:Folder
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Market Sales Support &amp; Readiness"
    id="a7b611bf-c1b1-4b0d-8d95-546f3c101875"
    documentation="Process Context&#xA;This process element represents part of the overall enterprise, modeled in business process terms, and can be applied (ie “instantiated&quot;) with other similar process elements for application within a specific organization or domain.&#xA;Brief Description&#xA;Market Sales Support &amp; Readiness processes ensure the support capability is in place to allow the CRM Fulfillment, Assurance and Billing processes to operate effectively.&#xA;Extended Description&#xA;Market Sales Support &amp; Readiness processes ensure the support capability is in place to allow the Market Sales Fulfillment, Assurance and Billing processes to operate effectively.  &#xA;The responsibilities of these processes include, but are not limited to:&#xA;• Provision of market and sales process infrastructure;, &#xA;• Policy support and decision support knowledge for  sales activity and sales interactions&#xA;• Management &amp; analysis of sales campaigns (including direct and outbound calling);&#xA;• Management and analysis of sales activity and sales opportunities (including funnel and prospect analysis and support);&#xA;• Maintaining and managing stocks of marketing collateral to be distributed using the Marketing Fulfillment processes;&#xA;• Maintaining inventories to support the sales data required by the FAB and CRM OS&amp;R processes &#xA;• Monitoring and reporting on the capabilities and costs of the individual Market FAB processes&#xA;• Longer-term trend analysis on sales  FAB processes in order to establish the extent to which enterprise targets for these processes are being achieved and/or the need for the processes to be modified.&#xA;These processes support the operational introduction of new processes and infrastructure to support new and/or enhanced sales capability and are responsible for conducting operations readiness testing and acceptance. They develop the procedures for the specific Fulfillment, Assurance and Billing processes and keep them up to date. After successful testing, these processes accept the new or enhanced process capabilities and manage a full-scale introduction for general availability."/>
