<archimate:Folder
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Track &amp; Manage Customer Bill Inquiry Resolution "
    id="1be66403-c4eb-4bca-ac20-e2a6f7002159"
    documentation="Process Context&#xA;This process element represents part of the overall enterprise, modeled in business process terms, and can be applied (ie “instantiated&quot;) with other similar process elements for application within a specific organization or domain.&#xA;Brief Description&#xA;Efficiently assign, coordinate and track specific customer bill inquiry analysis, bill adjustments and ensuring that appropriate credits and/or other agreed adjustments are made available to the adjustments processes activities, and escalate any open customer bill inquiries in jeopardy.&#xA;Extended Description&#xA;The objective of the Track &amp; Manage Customer Bill Inquiry Resolution processes is to efficiently assign, coordinate and track specific customer bill inquiry analysis, bill adjustments and ensuring that appropriate credits and/or other agreed adjustments are made available to the adjustments processes activities, and escalate any open customer bill inquiries in jeopardy. &#xA;&#xA;Responsibilities of these processes include, but are not limited to:&#xA;&#xA;- Scheduling, assigning and coordinating analysis and specific customer bill inquiry/complaint adjustment activities;&#xA;&#xA;- Modifying the customer bill inquiry/complaint status;&#xA;&#xA;- Canceling a customer bill inquiry when the specific request was related to a false billing event&#xA;&#xA;- Monitoring the jeopardy status of open customer bill inquiries, and escalating customer bill inquiries as necessary.&#xA;&#xA;Note that some specific product and/or service components may be owned and managed by other parties.  In these cases the Track &amp; Manage Customer Bill Inquiry Resolution process is responsible for initiating requests, through - the other parties Settlements &amp; Payments Management for resolution by the other parties of the specific bill inquiries/complaints. &#xA;&#xA;These processes will co-ordinate all the actions necessary in order to guarantee that all tasks are finished at the appropriate time and in the appropriate sequence.&#xA;The Track &amp; Manage Bill Inquiry Resolution processes will also inform the Close Customer Bill Inquiry processes by modifying the customer bill inquiry status to cleared when the specific customer bill inquiry/complaint issues have been resolved.&#xA;Explanatory&#xA;Reserved for future use."/>
