<archimate:Folder
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Party Revenue Management"
    id="eb8fe824-a6ab-4eb2-9926-eee45868d8a4"
    documentation="Brief Description&#xA;Manage party billing events, charge parties for products, manage bills/invoices, manage payments, sharing revenue, manage account balances, and handle bill/invoice inquiries.&#xA;Extended Description&#xA;Party Revenue Management manages party billing events, charging parties for products, managing bills/invoices, managing payments, sharing revenue, managing account balances, and handling bill/invoice inquiries.&#xA; &#xA;Party Billing Event Management enriches, guides, distributes, mediates, summarizes, accumulates, and analyzes billing events. These processes may occur in real-time, near real-time, or may be executed on a periodic basis. Party Charging assigns a value (monetary or other) to an event or product, or combination (bundle or aggregate) of the above. The charge may be either a credit or a debit and can be handled either online or offline.&#xA;&#xA;Party Bill/Invoice Management manages the party bill/invoice process, controls bills/invoices, manages the lifecycle of bills/invoices. Party Payment Management manages methods used by parties to make payments, administers payment plans, handles payments, and collects debt. &#xA;Party Revenue Sharing develops party revenue sharing models, prepares party revenue sharing agreements, determines party revenue shares, and reconciles party revenue shares.&#xA;&#xA;Party Account Balance Management manages, calculates, applies policies to manage, and manages functionality/interfaces for party account balances. Party Bill Inquiry Handling ensure the timely and effective resolution of all bill inquiries and complaints sent to and received from other parties.&#xA;&#xA;Party Charging assigns a value (monetary or other) to an event or product, or combination (bundle or aggregate) of the above. The charge may be either a credit or a debit and can be handled either online or offline.&#xA;&#xA;Party Payment Management manages methods used by parties to make payments, administers payment plans, handles payments, and collects debt.&#xA;&#xA;Party Revenue Sharing and Settlement develops party revenue sharing models, prepares party revenue sharing agreements, determines party revenue shares, and reconciles party revenue shares.&#xA;&#xA;Party Bill Inquiry Handling ensures the timely and effective resolution of all party bill inquiries and complaints initiated by an enterprise or initiated by another party, such as a partner. It includes the receiving and sending inquiries regarding a bill/invoice, managing the entire bill inquiry lifecycle, reporting changes to and updates to, and closure of a bill inquiry when all activities have been completed."/>
