<archimate:Folder
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Manage Customer Payments "
    id="36bb6052-8823-44c6-9b34-a3d296e73f15"
    documentation="Process Context&#xA;This process element represents part of the overall enterprise, modeled in business process terms, and can be applied (ie “instantiated&quot;) with other similar process elements for application within a specific organization or domain.&#xA;Brief Description&#xA;Collect payments made by the customer and reconcile the payments to the invoices.&#xA;Extended Description&#xA;The purpose of the Manage Customer Payments process is to collect payments made by the customer and reconcile the payments to the invoices.  This process is meant to match these payments with the services/invoices delivered to this customer. These processes can include credit/debit/EFT payments using various channels, either directly or through third parties, and cash or check payments, either directly or through third parties.&#xA;&#xA;In all the above cases these processes are responsible for the processes interacting with the customers and/or the third parties.  The processes are also responsible for establishing managing back-end bank accounts for receipt of the customer payments and for the transfer of funds collected by third parties.  These processes are responsible for reconciling the money received into the bank accounts against the payments expected in the invoices. Additionally these processes inform the Financial Management on all those payments for updating the ledger.&#xA;&#xA;These processes are responsible for establishing the requirements for, and managing any commercial arrangements agreed with, other parties.  Note that the other Party Capability Delivery process is used to deliver the commercial agreements.&#xA;&#xA;To the extent that processing of any payments is undertaken internally, i.e. check processing, these processes are responsible for managing the operation and quality of the internal processing.&#xA;&#xA;Where payments do not match invoices, this process is responsible for informing the Manage Customer Debt Collection Manage Debt Management processes of any underpayments, and the Bill Inquiry Handling processes for any over-payments .  Underpayments and overpayments are handled appropriately by these separate processes.&#xA;"/>
