<archimate:Folder
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Human Resources Management"
    id="d3e92a30-6c40-45bc-9ad8-02ae86d59e4b"
    documentation="Process Context&#xA;This process element represents part of the overall enterprise, modeled in business process terms, and can be applied (ie “instantiated&quot;) with other similar process elements for application within a specific organization or domain.&#xA;Brief Description&#xA;The Human Resources Management process grouping provides the human resources infrastructure for the people resources that the enterprise uses to fulfil its objectives. For example, Human Resources Management processes provide salary structures by level, coordinate performance appraisal and compensation guidelines and set policies in relation to people management, employee benefit programs, etc. Moreover it supports the definition of the organization of the enterprise and coordinates its reorganizations. Note that Human Resources Management processes are concerned with preparing people to carry out their assigned tasks (e.g., organizing, training, remuneration, recruiting, etc.).  The actual assignment of specific tasks is the responsibility of Work Force Management processes.&#xA;Extended Description&#xA;The Human Resources Management process grouping provides the human resources infrastructure for the people resources that the enterprise uses to fulfill its objectives. &#xA;For example, Human Resources Management processes provide salary structures by level, coordinate performance appraisal and compensation guidelines and set policies in relation to people management, employee benefit programs, etc.&#xA;Moreover it supports the definition of the organization of the enterprise and coordinates its reorganizations.&#xA;Note that Human Resources Management processes are concerned with preparing people to carry out their assigned tasks (e.g., organizing training, remuneration, recruiting, etc.). The actual assignment of specific tasks is the responsibility of Work Force Management processes."/>
