<archimate:Folder
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Manage Service Development "
    id="ce500931-0ce5-472e-b314-a6118a1532ae"
    documentation="Process Context&#xA;This process element represents part of the overall enterprise, modeled in business process terms, and can be applied (ie “instantiated&quot;) with other similar process elements for application within a specific organization or domain.&#xA;Brief Description&#xA;Ensure the co-coordinated development in line with the approved business case of all required new or enhanced service classes/components for that business case across the enterprise&#xA;Extended Description&#xA;The Manage Service Development processes ensure the co-coordinated development in line with the approved business case of all required new or enhanced service classes/components for that business case across the enterprise. These processes ensure that all operational processes and procedures, IT systems changes, network changes, channel changes, operational procedures, testing tools and procedures, etc. required to support the new service class/component are identified and developed. These processes ensure that the necessary documentation and training packages are produced to support the operation of the new service class. These processes also ensure that the required service level agreements and operational level agreements to support the detailed service specifications are developed and agreed for each service class deployed, and that any party operational support has been identified and agreed. These processes have both program/project management aspects and technical/operational specification aspects, with the detailed management of individual service class deployment managed by the Manage Service Deployment processes.&#xA;As well as developing new service classes these processes manage upgrades or enhancements to existing service classes, as the need to review operational and other support is also relevant for upgrading existing classes/components. &#xA;Note that management of major new or enhanced infrastructure delivery to support service development is managed within the Service Capability Delivery process."/>
