<archimate:BusinessProcess
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Create Customer QoS Report "
    id="8b0f2475-b1e1-4bff-a1aa-f382f7f87cf5"
    documentation="Process Context&#xA;This process element represents part of the overall enterprise, modelled in business process terms, and can be applied (i.e. “instantiated&quot;) with other similar process elements for application within a specific organization or domain.&#xA;Brief Description&#xA;Create a new customer QoS performance degradation report. A new customer QoS performance degradation report may be created as a result of specific customer initiated QoS performance degradation notifications, or at the request of analysis undertaken by other CRM, or SM&amp;O processes which detect that some form of deterioration or failure has occurred requiring an assessment of the performance of the specific customer purchased product offering. If the customer QoS performance degradation report is created as a result of a notification from customers or as a result of a request from other processes, the Create Customer QoS Performance Degradation Report processes are responsible for converting the received information into a form suitable for the Customer QoS/SLA Management processes, and for requesting additional information if required.&#xA;Extended Description&#xA;Not used for this process element&#xA;Explanatory&#xA; A new customer QoS performance degradation report may be created as a result of specific customer initiated QoS performance degradation notifications, or at the request of analysis undertaken by other CRM, or SM&amp;O processes which detect that some form of deterioration or failure has occurred requiring an assessment of the performance of the specific customer purchased product offering.&#xA;Mandatory&#xA;Create a new customer QoS performance degradation report.&#xA;Optional&#xA;Not used for this process element&#xA;Interactions&#xA; If the customer QoS performance degradation report is created as a result of a notification from customers or as a result of a request from other processes, the Create Customer QoS Performance Degradation Report processes are responsible for converting the received information into a form suitable for the Customer QoS/SLA Management processes, and for requesting additional information if required."/>
