<archimate:Folder
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Personalize Customer Profile for Retention &amp; Loyalty "
    id="e66f1ed4-1b6a-408b-8b97-5127f633cabe"
    documentation="Process Context&#xA;This process element represents part of the overall enterprise, modeled in business process terms, and can be applied (ie “instantiated&quot;) with other similar process elements for application within a specific organization or domain.&#xA;Brief Description&#xA;Provide the personalization opportunities for customers that will encourage them not to switch to another Service Provider&#xA;Extended Description&#xA;The purpose of this process is to provide the personalization opportunities for customers that will encourage them not to switch to another Service Provider. Personalization allows delivery of services that more closely match the customer’s need. Collection of Personalization Information also discourages switching since the customer would have to build up the same Personalized experience with the next Service Provider. &#xA;- Business Planning is essential to allow the Service Provider to match the customer’s future retention needs and potential acquisition needs, rather than just continuing with today’s known needs.&#xA;- Loyalty schemes allow tangible benefits to be offered to good customers in a mass-market.&#xA;- The process aims to ensure that all information is gathered and used to make the best decisions to retain those customers the Service Provider wants to retain, heighten satisfaction and maintain profitability.&#xA;&#xA;This process provides a source of data for performing loyalty and retention marketing campaigns, for retaining existing customers, promoting customer loyalty, winning back customers who have left. It utilizes predictive modeling software to analyze an account, and to return relevant scores, such as: churn score, up-sell score, cross-sell score, bad debt score and customer lifetime value score.  Moreover it utilizes scores for customer analysis and marketing campaign purposes.&#xA;"/>
