<archimate:Folder
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Create Customer Bill Invoice "
    id="cb0714b2-b784-4106-a444-d0f5e8711246"
    documentation="Process Context&#xA;This process element represents part of the overall enterprise, modeled in business process terms, and can be applied (ie “instantiated&quot;) with other similar process elements for application within a specific organization or domain.&#xA;Brief Description&#xA;Production of a timely and accurate invoice in accordance with the specific billing cycles and reflective of the final charges for services, together with any adjustments, delivered to the customer by the Service Provider and respective other  parties.&#xA;Extended Description&#xA;The primary purpose of the Create Customer Bill Invoice process is the production of a timely and accurate invoice in accordance with the specific billing cycles and reflective of the final charges for services, together with any adjustments, delivered to the customer by the Service Provider and respective  other parties.&#xA;This process contains the invoicing components of the Service Provider’s business. This includes the rendering/formatting of an invoice, the delivery of an electronic copy of an invoice to customers and the processes that verify invoice quality prior to distribution to the customer in electronic form, or to the process responsible for physical invoice production and distribution. The flow of this process can be viewed as an extension of the company’s e-business strategy. In this case, the Service Provider would render an invoice electronically, via the Internet for example.&#xA;Furthermore, this process provides specifications for the formatting of invoices in different ways and to achieve different publishing possibilities, and supports the creation of different invoice formats for different publication media. The process is further responsible for splitting and re-arranging invoices for customers (particularly customers with complex account structures) according to agreements made with these customers.&#xA;Additionally these processes store the customer invoice for a period of time to address regulation and/or internal requirements, during which they can be accessed to support any customer or regulator agency inquiries on bill invoices.&#xA;Explanatory&#xA;Reserved for future use.&#xA;"/>
