<archimate:Folder
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Manage Customer Debt Collection "
    id="6e5345a2-ec99-4565-9647-f34eb5da75bd"
    documentation="Process Context&#xA;This process element represents part of the overall enterprise, modeled in business process terms, and can be applied (ie “instantiated&quot;) with other similar process elements for application within a specific organization or domain.&#xA;Brief Description&#xA;Collect past due payments from the customer.&#xA;Extended Description&#xA;The purpose of the Manage Customer Debt Collection process is to collect past due payments from the customer.  This process monitors the amount due from the customer, i.e. check whether the payments are made on time, and implements necessary activities and policies to recover amounts overdue. &#xA;&#xA;The responsibilities of this process include, but are not limited to:&#xA;• Identifying invoices which are overdue for payment;&#xA;• Initiating and managing follow-up with customers having overdue amounts;&#xA;• Arranging and monitoring payment plans to allow customers to pay overdue amounts in installments;&#xA;• Initiating debt recovery activities in accordance with appropriate commercial practice and policies;&#xA;• Managing the aged customer debt portfolio;&#xA;• Establishing and managing customer debt profiles to assist in managing debt recovery and debt risk on a customer, product or customer group basis;&#xA;• Establishing and managing commercial arrangements with third parties for the recover of aged debt, and/or for the write-off and selling of parts of the debt portfolio to third parties&#xA;&#xA;Note that these processes may initiate a direct enquiry to the customer and attempt to manage the initial recovery through the Bill Inquiry Handling processes.  These processes use policies established by the Support Bill Payments &amp; Receivable Management process to direct any escalation of the recovery processes being employed. &#xA;&#xA;Note that where third party arrangements need to be put in place, these processes are responsible for establishing the requirements for, and managing any commercial arrangements agreed with, third party suppliers.  The Party Tender Management and Party Agreement Management processes are used deliver the commercial agreements."/>
