<archimate:BusinessProcess
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Track &amp; Manage Customer Order Handling "
    id="605e0247-7196-462c-8eda-f28ac6c31801"
    documentation="Process Context&#xA;This process element represents part of the overall enterprise, modeled in business process terms, and can be applied (ie “instantiated&quot;) with other similar process elements for application within a specific organization or domain.&#xA;Brief Description&#xA;Ensure customer provisioning activities are assigned, managed and tracked efficiently to meet the agreed committed availability date&#xA;Extended Description&#xA;The objective of the Track &amp; Manage Customer Order Handling processes is to ensure customer provisioning activities are assigned, managed and tracked efficiently to meet the agreed committed availability date.&#xA;Responsibilities of these processes include, but are not limited to:&#xA;• Scheduling, assigning and coordinating customer provisioning related activities;&#xA;• Generating the respective service order creation request(s) to Issue Service Orders based on specific customer orders;&#xA;• Escalating status of customer orders in accordance with local policy;&#xA;• Undertaking necessary tracking of the execution process;&#xA;• Adding additional information to an existing customer order;&#xA;• Modifying information in an existing customer order;&#xA;• Modifying the customer order status;&#xA;• Canceling a customer order when the initiating sales request is cancelled;&#xA;• Monitoring the jeopardy status of customer orders, and escalating customer orders as necessary&#xA;• Indicating completion of a customer order by modifying the customer order status. &#xA;Note that some specific product components may be delivered directly by other parties.  In these cases the Track &amp; Manage Customer Order Handling process is responsible for initiating requests, through other Party Requisition Management for the delivery by the other Party of the specific product components.&#xA;Explanatory&#xA;Reserved for future use.&#xA;Mandatory&#xA;Reserved for future use.&#xA;Optional&#xA;Reserved for future use.&#xA;Interactions&#xA;Reserved for future use."/>
